In this video, we'll show you how to
install Tessle onto your machine. You
will need to download the Tessle CLI,
which can be done using MPM. You'll need
a node version 22 or higher.
At a terminal, run npm install-g
passing in the URL shown. You can test
the CLI installation by running the
command tessle-help to check that
everything is working.
Once your installation is complete, you
can authenticate with Tessle by running
Tessle login.
This will redirect you to a browser for
you to authenticate and confirm the code
from your terminal.
Upon confirmation, you may close the
browser tab and your terminal will
notify you that your login was
successful.
You can test whether you are
authenticated at any time by running
Tessle. Who am I?
You should now have an authenticated
Tessle installation. Your next step is
to initialize Tessle in a project.